cygnet-infotech.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy

Home Privacy Policy

Cygnet is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring you have a positive experience on our website. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices for both online and offline data. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

#### Collection of your personal information

We will always tell you before we collect any Personal Information and inform you of the purpose of the collection. "Personal Information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, credit or debit card number, title, occupation, and other information required to provide a service, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. Some of the reasons we collect your Personal Information include:

  * Requesting service and support for our products or services
  * Placement of a transaction or order
  * Participation in an online survey
  * Participation in chat
  * collaboration efforts

#### Uses of your personal information

We will only use your Personal Information in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your Personal Information is used without your consent. Some of the ways we may use your Personal Information include:

  * To process your orders and deliver the products and services
  * To provide support and assistance for our products and services, including the provision of security patches.
  * To provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with shipping and billing information.
  * To provide customer feedback and support.
  * To conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better products and services to our customers and end users. Your completion of any questionnaires is voluntary.
  * To support recruitment inquiries.
  * To meet contract obligations.

#### Non-personal/anonymous information collection

In some instances, Cygnet may collect non-personal (aggregate or demographic) data through cookies, web logs etc. This information is used to better understand and improve the usability, performance, and effectiveness of the website. Please read the "Cookies" section below for more information.

#### Sharing your Personal Information

We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so.

We may share your Personal Information within Cygnet or any of its subsidiaries for purposes of data processing or storage.

We may also share your Personal Information with business partners, service vendors, authorized third-party agents or contractors in order to provide a requested service or transaction, including processing orders, processing credit card transactions, hosting websites, hosting event and seminar registration and providing customer support. We only provide these third parties with the minimum amount of Personal Information necessary to complete the requested service or transaction, and the third parties are not permitted to use your Personal Information except for limited purpose of completing the requested service or transaction.

We may respond to court orders or legal process by disclosing your Personal Information and other related information, if necessary. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We may collect and possibly share Personal Information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Cygnet's terms of use or as otherwise required by law.

While navigating Cygnet's website you may be directed to content or functionality that is hosted by a third-party supplier. This is typically done to host special events, such as contests. When information is collected on behalf of Cygnet exclusively, Cygnet's privacy policy will be referenced on the site and will govern how your information is used. For sites other than Cygnet the site owner's privacy policy will be referenced. It is Cygnet's practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with Cygnet's privacy & security policy.

#### Security of your Personal Information

Cygnet is committed to protecting personal information you share with us. We utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

When we transfer sensitive personal data (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit.

We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser. Please visit the Linksys website for more tips for using security features when connected to the Internet using a router.

#### Cookies

Like many websites, Cygnet uses technologies such as cookies, which allow us to make your visit to our website easier, more efficient and more valuable by providing you with customized experience and recognizing you when you return.

A cookie cannot read personal data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites; indeed, the only Personal Information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Accepting the cookies used on our website may give us access to information about your browsing behavior, which we may use to personalize your experience and track user traffic patterns, and to merge this info when you register. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. You may browse most of Cygnet's website without accepting cookies from Cygnet; however, some website functionality may be lost by disabling cookies on your computer. Other Cygnet web pages, particularly those which require a login and password, require cookies and cannot be used when you have disabled cookies in your browser.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website or via HTML-formatted emails, you can set your browser to warn you before it accepts cookies or refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser.

#### Data Retention

Cygnet will not retain your Personal Information longer than necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it has been collected or as required by applicable law or regulation.

#### Linked Websites

Our websites may provide links to other third-party websites which are outside our control and not covered by this policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these (and all) sites you visit.

#### Transfer of Personal Information

We may transfer your personal information to any of the Cygnet subsidiary worldwide or to the third parties acting on our behalf for the purposes of processing or storage.

#### Questions or Comments

Should you have any privacy related questions or comments related to this privacy policy, please sent an e-mail to: [webmaster@cygnet-infotech.com](mailto:webmaster@cygnet-infotech.com)

#### Policy Updates

Cygnet may amend this privacy policy at any time. We will post a notice whenever this privacy statement is materially changed. Your continued use of the Cygnet website after any change will signify and confirm your assent to those changes.

JavaScript is disabled.. Please enable it for Comment..
